ZooM studio Libre
presents
Umhhh, damn my car got broken...
Hi there!
Hi!
What an amazing car you have. It seeems
like you can travel at any terrain on it!
Yes, it's really so. I have constructed that car
by myself and it is fastest one in the world.
Look, I just need a good driver with
a car. Do you want to work on me?
OK. People call me Streetracer,
by the way.
Nice to meet you. I'm the famous traveler -
Boris Munchausen.
By accident, are you..
Yes, I'm his relative.
The Adventures of Boris Munchausen 1.01
I'm getting hungry, my stomach aches...
Look, there's someone sitting on the roadside.
Lets ask him is there any fast-food around.
Young man, can you tell us, is there
any place to eat nearby?
Of course there is! Go ride ahead, after 300
meters turn right...
Then turn right again. After 140 meters
turn left and park your car.
Then walk 8 meters along the parapet and you
will see "Scholar" eating-house.
But don't even think of ordering
mushroom soup there!
Because chef just drop sulfur-tuft
into this dish by accident.
How did you know that?
Oh, I do know a lot. I'm connecting to the military
satellite unit and watching the whole world.
Very cool! I might need a help of such talent.
Do you want to travel with us?
I'll stand the damages.
Of course. I've just got hungry right now.
Here he is!
He's got a gun, must be a hitman!
Get him! Grab him!
Gun, take the gun first!
Let's show him what is what!
Who do you think you are?
Why did you tried to kill us?
Oh, but...
Then why did you shoot?
Wait! Now I see, he did't tried to kill us!
He have made ricochet shot through
the stone on the roadside...
...and hit the fly, which was sitting on our
car near the right rear wheel...
...while we were riding
at the speed of 140 km/h.
You really surprising me!
Yes, that was a genuine perfect shot.
Thanks.
Without any doubt, he is a
greatest sniper in the world.
Well, I guess now there's no need
to introduce myself.
Look, I'm gathering a crew for one campaign.
And I need someone like you.
Do you want to join us? I pay well.
I love money!
Hurry, drive to this crowd!
Looks like there is a fight there...
Hey, what's happening here?
We were going to pull down this old building...
And this man just intentionally attacked us
and broke our machine with his fists.
What an amazing power! We need
this man. Sniper!
Yes?
Get this crowd away.
Roger that.
I need a person with such abilities like yours.
Do you want to travel with us?
With much pleasure. No one is happy
to see me here anyway.
This castle belongs to Salladin Hottab 4th,
from the family of Red.
Red?
Look at the flags.
I see.
I've heard of him. He is very greedy and evil person...
Yes, here's a file on him.
I know, but I think that we should
to have a go at visiting his castle.
I don't like this idea.
Yes, as I've heard,
it's easy to enter his castle...
...but if something will go wrong -
there's no chance to escape.
Man, I don't like this Saladin Hottab...
Still, I think we should go there. I'm sure we will
be able to fool this Salladin Hottab.
I will generously reward you all,
when we will return.
OK, we will go with you.
But we don't like it.
To be continued...